Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of...
James Quigley from Goldman Sachs.
Please go ahead.
Hello.
Thank you for taking the follow-up.
So earlier this year, Lutathera generics were cleared to launch by the courts in Delaware.
So I think a small impact overall on the sales perspective.
But how should we think about potential launches for future generic RLTs?
We don't have any experience here, obviously.
When thinking about generic impacts for RLTs, Novartis clearly has a number of competitive advantages.
But...
How are you thinking the markets could react or how could this play out if and when we see generic RLTs launching?
Thank you.
Yeah, thanks, James.
So as far as we know, neither of the two companies has received an FDA approval.
One is a 505B2 and one is a generic.
We continue to believe there needs to be a high threshold used by regulators to ensure that the same dose of radiation,
as being delivered to the tumor versus the originator brand that we have.
Now, that being said, we do believe that given our extensive network of supply and our ability to deliver on time in full
to physicians across the globe, but also across the United States,
we would see an impact from a generic launch, even with a lower price being brought into the market.
We think that RLT will behave very differently.
Then either small molecule and potentially biosimilars just for biologics,
just given the logistical complexity and as well as the expectation that physicians have that the medicine is delivered on time,
each time given the nature of the logistics for the office.
So, you know, we feel confident that from that said, we're not, we continue to work to keep bringing better medicine,
not only with the case of PSMA and prostate cancer, but we also follow on efforts as well.
For example, we have a lot of patients who have been diagnosed with PSMA and prostate cancer.
We have a lot of patients who have been diagnosed with PSMA and prostate cancer.
And really try to improve the treatment for neuroendocrine tumors as well,
follow-ons for Lutathera.
So stay tuned on that front as well.
Great, thank you.
Thank you.
Cool, next question.
Comes from the line of Ivan Fitcher from ZKB.
Please go ahead.